# Saravanan.R

UI/UX Designer

#### **CONTACT**

Bangalore. Madiwala

9

+91 9740317802

wegam04@gmail.com

wegam04.42web.io



#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth

12/03/1971

Nationality

Indian

Languages Known

English & Tamil

#### **OVER ALL EXPERIENCE**

UX Design

**UI** Design

Web/Graphic Design

Motion Graphic Design

## **TECHNICALL SKILLS**

Adobe XD, Figma

Photoshop Illustrator

••••

HTML5, CSS3

Bootstrap5

Dream weaver

••••

Flash / After Effect 2D, 3D, MAYA

••••

React UI

••••

Blender

### **EDUCATION**

Diploma in Animation (**Distance Education**) Tamilnadu Open University
Year 2010

B.Com (**Distance Education**) From Kalinga University Year 2005

#### Certification

Web Developer, Web Design and Graphic Design from Pentagon Global Solutions Limited

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have 8+ years of experience as a UX/UI Designer, Specialized in Web/Mobile interface designing, Graphic Designer, Application Clickable Prototyping, Splash Screen, Logo, Mockup, Creative Advertisement Banner, E-Mailer Design, Motion Graphics Design & HTML/CSS Develops.

Assisting in the implementation of UI concepts and design strategies

Can work with multiple teams, quick learner and open to learning new technologies.

#### **ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES**

Skilled in creating optimized graphics design and motion graphics design

Develops concepts from the brainstorming stage to final design, that includes sketches, storyboards, work flows, detailed wireframes and clickable prototypes for Android, IOS and Mobile Web Platforms

Working knowledge of responsive design for mobile device compatibility, cross-browser development, Basic React UI development and testing experience

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

DhruthZuci Tech Solutions Pvt Ltd. (Dec 2021 - July 2022)

Worked *UX/UI Designer*. My Roles web/mobile app, admin panel, banners, icons, logo design & html,css devlops. www.dztech.eshatechgroup.com

DXMinds Technologies. (July 2019 - Dec 2019)

Weroked *UX/UI Developer* My Roles web/mobile app, admin panel, banners, icons, logo design & html,css devlops. www.dxminds.com

Adadyn Technologies Pvt. Ltd. (Sep 2014 - May 2016)

Weroked **Associate UX Developer** My Roles web/mobile, product, banners, icons design & html,css devlops. www.adadyn.com

Salar Online Whole Sale Pvt Ltd. (Feb 2011 Feb 2014)

Weroked *Consultant Software Engineer* My Roles web pages, banners, e-mailer design & html,css devlops. www.20north.com | www.zansaar.com

Synergy Images (P) Ltd. (Apr2010 - Jul 2010)

Weroked *Sr. Web Developer* My Roles e-learning web pages designing, flash animations & html,css devloping. www.synergyimage.com

Emblazon Software (P) Ltd. (Sep 2009 - Apr2010)

Weroked *Sr. Web Designer* My Roles web template/pages design, flash animations & html,css devloping. www.emblazonsoft.com

Basil Communications (P) Ltd. (Dec 2007 - Feb 2009)

Weroked *Flash Animator/Developer* My Roles web template/pages, banners, designing, flash animations & html,css devlos. www.basilglobal.com

GDS International Pvt. Ltd. (Aug 2006 - Sept 2007)

Weroked **Web Designer** My Roles web template/pages, banners, design, flash animations & html,css devlops. www.gdsinternatinal.com

Maintec Technologies Pvt. (Aug 2005 - Aug 2006)

Weroked **Web Designer** My Roles web template/pages, banners, design & html,css devlops. www.maintec.com

ADDR.COM Technologies Pvt. (Dec 2003 - Aug 2005)

Weroked **Web/Graphic Designer** My Roles web template/pages design & html,css devlops. www.addr.com

#### **MY PROJECTS**

https://drive.google.com/open?id=1GIA8wvXgaWWTXA2M-8S7QJGelzmlKbRb

https://xd.adobe.com/view/d7771177-1630-47ff-8f3b-1478242f6ce2-8224/

https://app.zeplin.io/project/5de89c700a60864a78b4c2d9